<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../../Properties.xslt"?>
<Content xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Object id="gxui.Toolbar">
    <Group>
      <Name>General</Name>
      <Type>Main</Type>
      <Children>
        <Prop>
          <Id>Width</Id>
          <Name>Width</Name>
          <Type>Text</Type>
          <Default>100</Default>
			<Metadata />
			<Description>Control width.</Description>
        </Prop>
        <Prop>
          <Id>Height</Id>
          <Name>Height</Name>
          <Type>Text</Type>
          <Default>100</Default>
			<Metadata />
  			<Description>Control height.</Description>
        </Prop>
		<Group>
			<Name>Data Bindings</Name>
			<Children>
				<Prop>
					<Id>Data</Id>
					<Name>Data</Name>
					<Type>Custom</Type>
					<CustomType>Artech.Genexus.Common.CustomTypes.ControlAttVarReference, Artech.Genexus.Common</CustomType>
					<Metadata>
						<Value name="FlagSetValueMethod">SetData</Value>
						<Value name="FlagGetValueMethod">GetData</Value>
						<Value name="FlagDataTypeFilter">gxuiToolbar</Value>
						<Value name="FlagHideVariables">False</Value>
						<Value name="FlagHideAttributes">true</Value>
					</Metadata>
					<Description>
						A variable based on gxuiToolbar SDT, with the toolbar definition.
						* @property {gxuiToolbarItem[]} Data.Buttons A collection containing the list of toolbar items to render.
						* @property {String} Data.Buttons.Id An identifier for the item. When a button is pressed, the {@link #ButtonPressedId} property is set with the identifier set here, so you will know which button was pressed when the {@link #ButtonPressed} event is fired.
						* @property {String} Data.Buttons.Text The text of the toolbar item. Applies to Button, Menu, SplitButton, Group, Edit (shown as placeholder) and Text.
						* @property {String} Data.Buttons.Tooltip A tooltip to show when the mouse hovers the item. Applies to Button, Menu and SplitButton.
						* @property {String} Data.Buttons.Icon The path to an image to display in the item icon. Applies to Button, Menu and SplitButton.
						* @property {String} Data.Buttons.IconCls A css class which sets a background image to be used as the icon for this toolbar item. Applies to Button, Menu and SplitButton.
						* @property {gxuiToolbarItemIconAlign} Data.Buttons.IconAlign The side of the Button box to render the icon. Four values are allowed:
						*
						* - Top
						* - Right
						* - Bottom
						* - Left
						*
						* Applies to Button, Menu and SplitButton.
						* @property {String} Data.Buttons.Cls A CSS class to apply to the item's main element
						* @property {Boolean} Data.Buttons.EnableToggle True to enable pressed/not pressed toggling. Applies to Button and SplitButton.
						* @property {Boolean} Data.Buttons.Pressed True to start pressed (only if EnableToggle = true). Applies to Button and SplitButton.
						* @property {Boolean} Data.Buttons.Disabled True to start disabled. Applies to Button, Edit, Menu and SplitButton.
						* @property {gxuiToolbarItemTypes} Data.Buttons.Type Defines the type of the item (defaults to Button). The available types are:
						*
						* - Button: A simple button. Customisations include aligned icons, tooltips and sizing options.
						* - Text: A text to be rendered inside the toolbar.
						* - Edit: An edit field. Its value can be retrieved through the {@link #EditFieldValue} property.
						* - Fill: A non-rendering placeholder item. When used, all items at its right side are right aligned.
						* - Separator: Adds a vertical separator bar between toolbar items. It can't be a direct child of a Group item.
						* - Menu: A button that opens a menu. The menu options are set through the Items property. An arrow is automatically added to the button.
						* You can change the alignment of the arrow using the ArrowAlign property.
						* - SplitButton: A split button that provides a built-in dropdown arrow used to display a dropdown menu that provides additional options to the primary button action.
						* - Group: A container for arranging a group of related Buttons in a tabular manner. The items inside the group are set through the Items property.
						* By setting RowSpan and ColSpan properties in child items, complex layouts can be accomplished within the table.
						* The basic concept of building a layout inside the group is conceptually very similar to building up a standard HTML table.
						* You simply add each item that you want to include along with any span attributes specified as the special config properties of RowSpan and ColSpan
						* which work exactly like their HTML counterparts. Rather than explicitly creating and nesting rows and columns as you would in HTML,
						* you simply specify the total column count in the GroupColumns property and start adding items in their natural order from left to right, top to bottom.
						* The layout will automatically figure out, based on the column count, rowspans and colspans, how to position each item within the table.
						* Just like with HTML tables, your rowspans and colspans must add up correctly in your overall layout or you'll end up with missing and/or extra items.
						* Example usage:
						*
						*         gxuiToolbar
						*         {
						*             Buttons
						*             {
						*                 Item
						*                 {
						*                     Text = 'File'
						*                     Type = gxuiToolbarItemTypes.Group
						*                     GroupColumns = 3
						*                     Items
						*                     {
						*                         Item
						*                         {
						*                             Id = !'New'
						*                             Text = 'New'
						*                             Type = gxuiToolbarItemTypes.Button
						*                             Scale = gxuiToolbarItemScale.Large
						*                             RowSpan = 3
						*                         }
						*                         Item
						*                         {
						*                             Id = !'Open'
						*                             Text = 'Open'
						*                             Type = gxuiToolbarItemTypes.Button
						*                             Scale = gxuiToolbarItemScale.Large
						*                             RowSpan = 3
						*                         }
						*                         Item
						*                         {
						*                             Id = !'Close'
						*                             Text = 'Close'
						*                             Type = gxuiToolbarItemTypes.Button
						*                         }
						*                         Item
						*                         {
						*                             Id = !'CloseKB'
						*                             Text = 'Close KB'
						*                             Type = gxuiToolbarItemTypes.Button
						*                         }
						*                         {
						*                             Id = !'Exit'
						*                             Text = 'Exit'
						*                             Type = gxuiToolbarItemTypes.Button
						*                         }
						*                     }
						*                 }
						*             }
						*         }
						*
						* @property {Boolean} Data.Buttons.Hidden True to start hidden.
						* @property {Number} Data.Buttons.GroupColumns Groups show toolbar items in a tabular manner. The total number of columns to create in the table is set through this property. If not specified it will be rendered into a single row using one column per item. Applies only to Group.
						* @property {gxuiToolbarItemScale} Data.Buttons.Scale The size of the Button. Three values are allowed:
						*
						* - Small - Results in the button element being 16px high.
						* - Medium - Results in the button element being 24px high.
						* - Large - Results in the button element being 32px high.
						*
						* Applies to Button, Menu and SplitButton.
						* @property {gxuiToolbarItemArrowAlign} Data.Buttons.ArrowAlign The side of the button box to render the arrow if the button has an associated menu. Two values are allowed:
						*
						* - Right
						* - Bottom
						*
						* Applies to Menu and SplitButton.
						* @property {Number} Data.Buttons.RowSpan Number of rows the item will span. Only applies to items that are direct children of a Group item.
						* See the documentation about the Group item type for detailed information.
						* @property {Number} Data.Buttons.ColSpan Number of columns the item will span. Only applies to items that are direct children of a Group item.
						* See the documentation about the Group item type for detailed information.
						* @property {Boolean} Data.Buttons.AskConfirmation Indicates if the user should be prompted for confirmation when a button is pressed, before executing the {@link #ButtonPressed} event. If the user confirms, the event is executed.
						* @property {gxuiToolbarItem.Confirmation} Data.Buttons.Confirmation Configuration properties for the confirmation dialog.
						* @property {String} Data.Buttons.Confirmation.OKButtonText Text for the OK button (defaults to 'OK')
						* @property {String} Data.Buttons.Confirmation.CancelButtonText Text for the Cancel button (defaults to 'Cancel').
						* @property {String} Data.Buttons.Confirmation.Message (required) Text for the dialog message.
						* @property {String} Data.Buttons.Confirmation.Title Text for the dialog title.
						* @property {String} Data.Buttons.Items Collection of children items of the button. Applies to Menu, SplitButton and Group.
					</Description>
				</Prop>		
		     </Children>
		</Group>
		<Prop>
			<Id>ButtonPressedId</Id>
			<Name>ButtonPressedId</Name>
			<Type>Text</Type>
			<Default></Default>
			<Metadata>
			<Value name="FlagScope">Runtime</Value>
			</Metadata>
			<Description>The identifier of the button that was pressed. This property is useful when the {@link #ButtonPressed} event is fired.</Description>
		</Prop>			
		<Prop>
			<Id>EditFieldValue</Id>
			<Name>EditFieldValue</Name>
			<Type>Text</Type>
			<Default></Default>
			<Metadata>
			<Value name="FlagScope">Runtime</Value>
			</Metadata>
			<Description>The value of the edit field that was lost focus or where the Enter key was pressed.</Description>
		</Prop>			
      </Children>
    </Group>
  </Object>
</Content>