<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../../Properties.xslt"?>
<Content xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
	<Object id="gxui.Menu">
		<Group>
			<Name>General</Name>
			<Type>Main</Type>
			<Children>
				<Prop>
					<Id>Menu</Id>
					<Name>Menu</Name>
					<Type>Custom</Type>
					<CustomType>Artech.Genexus.Common.CustomTypes.ControlAttVarReference, Artech.Genexus.Common</CustomType>
					<Metadata>
						<Value name="FlagSetValueMethod">SetMenu</Value>
						<Value name="FlagGetValueMethod">GetMenu</Value>
						<Value name="FlagDataTypeFilter">gxuiToolbarItem</Value>
						<Value name="FlagHideVariables">False</Value>
						<Value name="FlagHideAttributes">true</Value>
					</Metadata>
					<Description>
						A variable based on a collection of gxuiToolbarItem SDT, with the menu definition.
						* @property {String} Menu.Id An identifier for the item. When a menu option is pressed, the {@link #ItemClickedId} property is set with the identifier set here, so you will know which menu option was pressed when the {@link #ItemClick} event is fired.
						* @property {String} Menu.Text The text of the menu option. Applies to Button, Menu and Text.
						* @property {String} Menu.Tooltip A tooltip to show when the mouse hovers the item. Applies to Button and Menu.
						* @property {String} Menu.Icon The path to an image to display in the item icon. Applies to Button and Menu.
						* @property {String} Menu.IconCls A css class which sets a background image to be used as the icon for this menu option. Applies to Button and Menu.
						* @property {String} Menu.Cls A CSS class to apply to the item's main element
						* @property {Boolean} Menu.Disabled True to start disabled. Applies to Button, and Menu.
						* @property {gxuiToolbarItemTypes} Menu.Type Defines the type of the item (defaults to Button). The supported types are:
						*
						* - Button: A simple button. Customisations include aligned icons, tooltips and sizing options.
						* - Text: A text to be rendered inside the toolbar.
						* - Separator: Adds a vertical separator bar between toolbar items. It can't be a direct child of a Group item.
						* - Menu: A button that opens a menu. The menu options are set through the Items property. An arrow is automatically added to the button.
						* @property {Boolean} Menu.Hidden True to start hidden.
						* @property {gxuiToolbarItem[]} Menu.Items Collection of children items of the menu option. Applies to Menu only.
					</Description>
				</Prop>
				<Prop>
					<Id>ItemClickedId</Id>
					<Name>ItemClickedId</Name>
					<Type>Text</Type>
					<Default></Default>
					<Metadata>
						<Value name="FlagScope">Runtime</Value>
					</Metadata>
					<Description>The identifier of the menu option that was pressed. This property is useful when the {@link #ItemClick} event is fired.</Description>
				</Prop>
			</Children>
		</Group>
	</Object>
</Content>